不好? 那好吧
No? Oh. Well, okay.
好 那么
Okay, then.
先生们 请你们出去
Eh, gentlemen, give us a minute.
我以为你去了著名的"沃尔玛"
I thought you were going to this famous "Walmart."
它被高估了
Overrated.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我们还有沙拉
We have a salad course.
你想要沙拉吗?
Would you like a salad course?
我...不用了
don't need a salad course. Um...
我受宠若惊
I'm very flattered.
你是一位不可思议的歌手 舞者..
You're an incredible singer, and dancer...
以及说唱歌手
and rapper.
但你还是没回答我的问题
There's still an elephant in the room, though.
抱歉 我离开一下
Excuse me just a moment.
他的真名是什么?
What's his real name?
你还在纠结那个?
You're still on that?
我不理解
I don't understand,
我们的邮件交流十分顺利
our emails were so promising.
我知道那种感觉
I know what it's like.
- 你确定?  - 当然
- You do? - Sure.
在酒店被一个有魅力的领导宠爱...
Being pampered by a charismatic leader in a hotel room...
甚至使他都觉得他爱上了你
where maybe even he thinks he's in love with you.
另外 权利是醉人的
Plus, power is intoxicating.
- 伏特加也是  - 那不就是约会的目的嘛?
- So is vodka. - Isn't that what dates are for?
你睁一只眼闭一只眼 试图看到男人的优点
You squint at things and try to see the best in a guy.
我喜欢相信别人
I like giving people the benefit of the doubt.
我确实喜欢
I do.
等下 你现在是进入角色了吗?
Wait, are you in character right now?
时常 我总是不在状态
Often. I lose track.
你都没有在网上搜索他的信息?
You didn't even Google him?
我不认为我需要那么做
I didn't think I needed to.
我们已经邮件来往了几个月了
We'd been emailing for months.
- 我以为...  - 妹子 没那么难的
- I thought... - Girl, it's not that hard.
尤其是在克里米亚事件之后
Especially after Crimea.
我一开始进来时
When I walked in here,
他是戴着结婚戒指的
he was wearing a wedding ring.
但当我再次确认时 戒指不见了
But when I checked again, he wasn't.
我发誓刚刚还在的
And then I swear he just was.
他对如何表现自己有些犹豫
He can be a little bit indecisive about his self-presentation.
妹子 讲真 你在干啥?
Girl. Seriously, what are you doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
你知道吗 你是一个成年人
You know what, you're a grown woman.
自己弄明白
Figure it out.
纳森·伊万诺维奇
Alas, Nathan Ivanovich.
我从不认识你
I never knew you.
我不知道是什么 只知道什么应该
I don't know what is, only what seems to be.
或者不应该
Or not to be.
我们到底是怎么支撑着这沉重的生活
How do we even hold up this heavy life,
我已经减轻到
which I myself have had a hand in reducing
只要基本的生存需求
down to bare survival
生存
Survival.
生存很难 但是也是有可能
Survival sucks, but it is possible
死亡更糟糕
death is worse.
我参与过的所有的事情中
Of all the things I have been party to,
我作为一个有能力...
I, who have the power
改变历史进程的人
to bend the course of history,
居然被区区一个女人...
have come up against a problem...
给问倒了...
one small woman...
我该以什么身份面对她呢
and who to be to her.
我应该对她真诚一点
I should be real to her.
除非我已被深深腐蚀
Unless I am corroded to my depth.
我已经超负荷了 我感觉到
I am out of scale. I feel myself so.
我应该再试试
I should give it a whirl.
你结婚了吗?
Are you married?
是 也不是
Well, yes and no.
我刚刚谷歌了你的信息
I just Googled you.
如果我没弄错的话
And if I'm not mistaken,
你有妻子
you have a wife.
你能上网查到我?
You can Google me?
是的
Yeah. I can.
并且很容易
It was pretty easy, too.
如果你没用那么多别名的话
It would've been easier if you didn't have
那将会更容易
so many pseudonyms.
那么 你和你的妻子有什么约定吗?
So, do you and your wife have some sort of arrangement?
有也没有
Eh, yes and no.
你到底什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
我意思是 有一些吧
Well, I mean, sort of.
这种事没有模棱两可
There's no sort of.
你要么结婚了要么是没有
Either you're married or you aren't,
你和你的妻子要么有约定要么没有
or your wife and you have an arrangement or you don't.
不要沮丧
Don't get upset.
我没有沮丧
I'm not upset.
我只是想知道
I just need to know.
我意思是 我不会随便跟人上床的
I mean, I'm not above casual sex,
但我想我们都清楚那不是我们在这的原因
but I think we both know that's not why we're here.
我真的很喜欢和你通信 喜欢和你聊天
I really liked writing to you and I like talking to you
并且我们现在在酒店里 我真的想知道
and now we're in a hotel room and I need to know.
那你之前为什么不问我结婚没呢
Why didn't you ask me before about being married.
因为你点了那个选项
Because you checked the box.
什么选项?
What box?
单身的选项
The one about being single.
错了
Oops.
关于性的问题你也撒谎了是吗?
Did you lie about the sex questions, too?
没有 当然没有
No. No, no, no, no. Of course not.
绝对没有
Never.
这样会扰乱算法
It would mess up the algorithm.
如果你像对待工作 家庭或者其他事情那样
What's the point of having a girlfriend or a mistress
对我保密 那么做你的女友或情妇
or whatever it is you want me to be
或是你希望我做的角色
if you're just gonna act the same way you do
又有什么意义呢?
at home, or at work, or whatever?
我知道了
I know.
这是我人生的悲哀
This is the tragedy of my life.
你知道我人生有多悲哀吗?
Do you know the tragedy of my life?
不
No.
我知道 因为你重来没有问过我
I know. Because you never asked me.
你在网上的时候真是很有魅力
You're really charming on the Internet,
但是见到面你却不问过我的事
but then in person, you don't even ask me
比如我悲哀的人生
shit like what's the tragedy of my life
或是双亲是否健在
or even if my parents are alive.
我知道你父母还活着 你在邮件说过
I know your parents are alive because it came up
你回威斯康辛州那次
in the email when you went back to Wisconsin.
回去参加我父亲的葬礼
For my dad's funeral.
英语不是我的母语
This is not my first language.
你就不能试着说实话吗?
Don't you even wanna try being honest
就一天 仅仅为了体验也不行?
just for like one day, like for an experiment?
听着 我需要一些真实的人在我身边
Look, I need to be around someone real,
达拉 我能从你身上感受到
and, Darla, I can feel that about you.
你是如此的真实
You are so freaking real.
而我...所做的一切都是制造混乱...
And... all I do is create chaos...
并且引人瞩目...
which is remarkably effective...
但是你是真实的
but you are actually, truly real.
这就是我所需要的
And that-that is what I need.
这就是我在这里的原因
That is why I am here.
抱歉... 我得走了
I'm sorry. I... I'm gonna go.
不 不 求你了 不要
No, no, no, no, no! Please, please.
求你再呆一会吧
Please stay just for a little longer.
再吃点甜点吧
Hey, stay for dessert.
美味的白巧克力慕斯
A wonderful white chocolate mousse.
我得走了
I need to go.
天呐
Oh, my God.
不 不
No, no, no,
他们说你这样离开不安全
they are saying that it is not safe for you
因为有...山火
to leave because there is a... wildfire.
我没看见哪里有山火
I don't see any wildfire.
对了 他们说外面有枪击
Oh, yes. They are saying there is a shooting.
你现在走不安全
It's not safe for you to go.
我什么都没听到 你听到了?
I didn't hear any shooting, did you?
恐怖的枪击
Some threat of shooting
或是炸弹威胁之类的
or a bomb threat or something like that.
我不信
I don't believe you.
好吧
All right.
天呐!
Oh, my God!
他们从外面锁住了?
They lock it from the outside?
不 拜托 请冷静
No, no, please, please relax.
你会弄坏门把手的
You'll break the knob.
谢谢你留下来
Thank you for staying.
这对我来说很重要
It means a lot to me.
我的生活有太多悲剧可以说
There is so much to say about the tragedy of my life.
根据你所写
And from your writing,
我相信你能理解我的痛苦
I believe you will really be able to understand the pains
它的根源是作为
that come from being
一个如此重要的政治家
such an important political technologist.
你看 从我是个孩子时就开始了
You see, it started when I was a child.
我在山上的学校上学
At the academy in the mountains,
乌拉尔山脉
the Ural Mountains.
它很漂亮...
They can be beautiful...
但也很致命
but they can be deadly.